{
"questions":[
    {
      "questionId": 1,
      "question": "A computer program is a piece of _______?",
      "choices": ["hardware",
                  "underwear",
                  "software",
                  "hard drive"],
      "correctChoice": "software"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 2,
        "question": "Devices that are connected to computers, such as printers, scanners and modems, are called what?",
        "choices": ["peripherals",
                    "formats",
                    "apps",
                    "icons"],
        "correctChoice": "peripherals"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 3,
        "question": "What do we call a specific computer record containing data or a small program?",
        "choices": ["a keybind",
                    "an icon",
                    "a format",
                    "a file"],
        "correctChoice": "a file"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 4,
        "question": "What do we call the part of a computer that stores programs and information?",
        "choices": ["the soft disk",
                    "the hard disk",
                    "the hotspot",
                    "the notebook"],
        "correctChoice": "the hard disk"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 5,
        "question": "What do we call a program for exploring the Web and viewing websites?",
        "choices": ["a driver",
                    "a passenger",
                    "a browser",
                    "a scanner"],
        "correctChoice": "a browser"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 6,
        "question": "To open a particular folder, file or app, you just have to click on its what?",
        "choices": ["font",
                    "pixel",
                    "icon",
                    "none of the above"],
        "correctChoice": "icon"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 7,
        "question": "RAM, ROM and cache are different types of _______ that computers can use.",
        "choices": ["fonts",
                    "Wi-Fi",
                    "files",
                    "memory"],
        "correctChoice": "memory"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following allows wireless data communication?",
        "choices": ["a USB Flashdrive",
                    "an ethernet cable",
                    "a Bluetooth connection",
                    "an anti-virus app"],
        "correctChoice": "a Bluetooth connection"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 9,
        "question": "What do people go to public hotspots for?",
        "choices": ["Internet access",
                    "cable TV",
                    "software bugs",
                    "free viruses"],
        "correctChoice": "Internet access"
    },
    {
        "questionId": 10,
        "question": "A computer's _______ is called its heart or 'brains' because it's where data is processed.",
        "choices": ["ROM",
                    "CPU",
                    "GPU",
                    "RAM"],
        "correctChoice": "CPU"
    }
  ]
}